rentboy.com 2014-02-14

# Rentboy - Privacy Policy

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact ERS via electronic mail at [support@rentboy.com](mailto:support@rentboy.com) or by mail directed to:

Easy Rent Systems, Inc.  
6 West 14th Street, Suite 4W  
New York, New York 10011

## Information we may gather from you

When you visit www.rentboy.com , we may collect information about your visit.  We may collect your IP address (or the address of your proxy), browser type, domain name, and we may log the length of time of your visit and the number of times you visit and your manner of use of this site.  We may further use tracking software (including, without limitation, tracking pixels) to monitor your use of this site.  By using this site, you expressly permit us to collect and use the information we collect from you.  When you click to a third party site, such third party site may have policies distinct from our own.  Please review the policies of such third party site to ascertain applicable policies.

Generally, electronic information that we log is used to gather non-specific demographic information about our visitors and generally such information is used to personalize the information you see displayed on this site.  Your IP address may also be used to support and identify your computer so that we can make your visit to our site more enjoyable.  Your IP address (or the address of your proxy) may, in certain instances, be linked to personal identifiable information (for example, without limitation, by your request that we store information on certain listings posted on this site or by your use of our messaging services).

Depending on the nature of your visit to this site, we may collect your personal identifying information (including, for example, your name, address and email address) and, to the extent applicable, if you are making a purchase from us and/or a payment through this site, we will require you to provide us with billing and financial information (like your billing address, telephone number and credit account or credit card number).  We link your payment information to your IP address and other personal identifying information, as applicable.  We may use third parties to verify and authorize credit card transactions made through this site.  The billing address and telephone number you provide will generally only be used for verification purposes, while your email address may be used for multiple purposes, including, verification, log in and mailing lists.

We may use your personal identifying information to send you information about additional offers or services. In such cases, we may share your personal and contact information with our team of agents and affiliates to more properly service you.

We may use cookies to store information.  Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive.  Cookies are text files that are commonly deposited by sites on a user’s hard drive.  The file identifies a user’s computer and can record a user’s preferences and certain other information.  Generally, cookies make it easier for you to interact with a site.  You may be able to prevent our collection of such data by setting your browser to reject cookies but blocking cookies may adversely affect your ability to interact with this site.  You may be able to find your own cookie files on your hard disk and see what information is being stored in such files and by which sites and may be able to delete information contained in such cookie files.  To find a cookie file, search for cookie.txt, cookies or MagicCookie.

## Security

We use our reasonable efforts to protect the data we collect from you against unauthorized access.  When you place orders, make purchases and/or access your personal identifying account information, we offer the use of a secure socket layer (SSL).  A secure socket layer is used to assist in the encryption of information.  (You may be able to discern whether your information is being transmitted via SSL by making certain that the Uniform Resource Locator (URL) is prefixed with “https” rather than “http” and that a padlock icon is displayed on the lower right corner of your browser (for transmissions via MS Internet Explorer)).  If you make a payment through this site, you may be directed to a third party site for payment processing or verification; the policies of such third party site may apply to the processing of your transaction.We are not  responsible for the policies of any third party sites.

## Correct/Update

During the transaction process, we will endeavor to permit you to review, change, or delete the information that you have submitted.  We encourage you to update your information whenever it changes.

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.

  1. Online at [www.rentboy.com](http://www.rentboy.com/).
  2. You can send email to [support@rentboy.com](mailto:support@rentboy.com)
  3. You can send mail to the following postal address: 

Customer Service  
Easy Rent Systems, Inc,  
6 West 14th Street, Ste. 4W  
New York, New York 10011

We welcome your questions and comments.  Please send e-mails to [support@rentboy.com](mailto:support@rentboy.com)

## Privacy Changes

Whenever we change our privacy policy, we will make reasonable commercial efforts to promptly post a notice on this site indicating that new information has been posted.  If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will take reasonable commercial efforts to promptly notify you by way of email.  To the extent practicable, we will endeavor to offer you a choice as to whether or not we use information previously collected in a different manner.  We will take reasonable commercial efforts to use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

## Required Disclosure of Information

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may disclose your personal information in certain instances.  We will make such disclosure when we believe, in our sole and absolute discretion, that such disclosure or other action is necessary or desirable to comply with applicable law, legal process and/or in connection with any civil and/or criminal investigation by us or any third party.  We also reserve the right to disclose your personal information to protect our rights and property, including, without limitation, in connection with any investigation by us of fraud or in the event we believe disclosure to be necessary or desirable to otherwise protect the users of this site and others.  We reserve the right to disclose your personal identifying information, in our sole and absolute discretion, when we believe it necessary to do so.

## Privacy Disputes

Any dispute over privacy is subject to the terms of use, provisions and conditions for this site.  Please click here to view such terms of use, provisions and conditions.

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about the terms of use, provisions and conditions set forth herein, our practices, or your dealings with this site, please feel free to contact us at:

Easy Rent Systems, Inc.  
6 West 14th Street, Suite 4W  
New York, New York 10011  
support@rentboy.com

**_Additional Terms relating to 28 U.S.C. § 2257 Compliance_**

This site relies on the language of 18 U.S.C. § 2257 and 28 C.F.R. § 75 and on the decision of the United States Court of Appeals in Sundance Associates, a Colorado corporation v. Janet Reno, in her official capacity as Attorney General of the United States (139 F.3d 804, 10th Circuit, 1998), which held that entities which merely distribute content, and have no role in procuring or producing content, are not primary or secondary producers (as such terms are defined in 18 U.S.C. § 2257 and 28 C.F.R. § 75) and, accordingly, are exempt from record keeping requirements.  The content supplied on this site is posted voluntarily by the users of this site.  ERS, therefore, does not participate in the production of the photographs disseminated on this site.  Nonetheless information is herein provided as to where such records are located.

18 U.S.C. § 2257 Compliance Notice:   All models, actors, actresses and other persons that appear in any visual depiction of actual or simulated sexual conduct were over the age of eighteen (18) years at the time of the creation of such depictions.  Some of the aforementioned depictions appearing or otherwise contained in or at the website may contain visual depictions of actual sexually explicit conduct made before July 3, 1995, and, as such, are exempt from the requirements set forth in 18 U.S.C. § 2257 and 28 C.F.R. § 75.  With regard to the remaining depictions of actual sexual conduct appearing or otherwise contained in or at this site, the records required pursuant to 18 U.S.C. 2257 and 28 C.F.R. § 75 are kept by the custodian of records listed below.

The owners and operators of this site are not the primary or secondary producers of any of the visual content contained in the site. The custodian of records for this site is:

Easy Rent Systems, Inc.  
6 West 14th Street, Ste. 4W  
New York, New York 10011
